[
    {
        "question": "1, 3, 9, 27, __",
        "options": ["A. 54", "B. 81", "C. 108", "D. 243"],
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "2, 6, 20, 42, __",
        "options": ["A. 64", "B. 78", "C. 84", "D. 90"],
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "1024, 512, 256, 128, __",
        "options": ["A. 64", "B. 32", "C. 48", "D. 72"],
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "question": "1, 4, 9, 16, 25, 36, __",
        "options": ["A. 49", "B. 52", "C. 54", "D. 64"],
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "question": "3, 5, 11, 21, __",
        "options": ["A. 30", "B. 35", "C. 41", "D. 43"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "150, 140, 120, 90, __",
        "options": ["A. 50", "B. 55", "C. 60", "D. 65"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "4, 16, 36, 64, __",
        "options": ["A. 100", "B. 144", "C. 125", "D. 81"],
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "question": "6, 11, 20, 37, __",
        "options": ["A. 58", "B. 72", "C. 63", "D. 79"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "1, 3, 7, 15, 31, __",
        "options": ["A. 57", "B. 63", "C. 55", "D. 69"],
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "3, 8, 15, 24, __",
        "options": ["A. 35", "B. 36", "C. 39", "D. 48"],
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "question": "1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, __",
        "options": ["A. 11", "B. 12", "C. 13", "D. 14"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "2, 8, 32, 128, __",
        "options": ["A. 256", "B. 512", "C. 1024", "D. 2048"],
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "7, 21, 14, 42, 28, __",
        "options": ["A. 56", "B. 84", "C. 48", "D. 72"],
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "10, 17, 26, 37, __",
        "options": ["A. 48", "B. 50", "C. 51", "D. 53"],
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "question": "3, 9, 27, 81, __ ",
        "options": ["A. 162", "B. 243", "C. 324", "D. 405"],
        "answer": "B"
    }
]